>> It's kind of funny because I mean when it comes down to it, it's hot sauce, right? But I've become pretty obsessed with it.
>> It's absolutely iconic, and I think it's completely unintentional, too. >> Three very distinct syllables. >> See-rah-cha. >> I just
love that bold flavor. >> Ooh, ha ha. It's yummy! >> Almost everyone love my product.
>> It has this cult following. >> I feel very proud. >> Thank you for making the world's greatest sauce. >> Ha ha
ha ha. >> Most people don't know where Sriracha came from. You need to go eat Sriracha the way
we eat Sriracha. >> I didn't know
Sriracha was popular in the U.S. I'm really surprised!
>> A little mind-blown when I heard the whole story
behind it. >> Dude, just amazing story. >> Sriracha! >> I continue to make my good product for
my fans. Until some day, they don't like, I stop to make.